♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
[Emerson] What's that? Atomic bomb?
[Paldo] That's a bazooka!
Avoid it, or we'll be dust!
[Atoy] Okay, okay, okay! I'll go to you!
[whooshes, then explosion]
PREVIOUSLY
- [grunts]
- [tires screeching]
[Paldo] You need to make sure you live!
You need to tell Atoy the truth!
What truth?!
[grunts, groans]
It's about your father.
[Paldo] The day your father
got hit-and-run,
you were really the target
because you compromised
the shipment at the port.
You ran over my father?
[Paldo gasps] Not me.
- [Atoy] Who?
- [Paldo] Red.
[explosion]
[Mongki] Boss, Paldo escaped.
[Red] Where does Paldo live?
Let's visit him.
[Atoy] All this time,
the people who killed my father
are the ones we deal with!
Are you also looking for Paldo?
[Nestor] I've been calling,
but no one's answering.
Atoy always asks me about you.
He's sad that you're ignoring him.
You're just saying that.
[car revving]
Ibyang! Help!
[Munggo] She was taken to the hospital!
- She almost got run over earlier!
- [Ame] Huh?
Let's make up now.
It's just you who's mad at me.
[Atoy] It's just you, really.
[Emerson] It's a blessing in disguise.
Think about it.
Had you rushed to confront Red earlier,
you probably would have been killed there.
He's lucky
because he'll still make
it until tomorrow.
[music fades]
[cool upbeat music playing]
[giggling, indistinct chattering]
[Jona] What's yours?
I've been here a while.
- [Mona] Mona.
- [Jona] Hi, I'm Jona.
[Jona] Hello! He smiled!
He's missing a tooth. But it's fine.
- [overlapping chatter]
- [in English] Excuse me.
Oh.
You were with Karla earlier, right?
Which one of you is Denden?
- Den--
- Ah, Denden.
She already went home.
She suddenly saw her ex,
so, she hurriedly left.
[Mona] But you're Gavin, right?
Karla's friend.
Oh my gosh, it's him!
Take care of Karla, okay.
We're moving to other guys!
Yes, yes. Ah--
[Jona] Bring her home safe, okay?
- Or else, Brother Atoy will be mad!
- [Mona] Yes.
- [Jona] He'll be mad. Oh, take care…
- Okay, fine.
- [Jona] Bye.
- So, Be? We're leaving.
Let's go. Bye, handsome!
He's following us.
[Jona] Don't follow us.
[Jona exclaims]
[Cathy] Karla, go. Go on.
[in English] Make friends. Have fun!
- [cool upbeat music playing]
- [lively chatter]
[in English] Have fun! [chuckles]
[Cathy] Let her.
[indistinct chatter]
Um, guys, let's go to another place.
‪[indistinct]
Huh?
Babe, um, let's go to another place.
Where's Karla?
Uh, somewhere over there
with her friends, maybe.
[in English] Let's go.
[in English] Uh, with two boys.
Why did you leave her with strangers?
What if something happens to her?
[in English] Why are you so mad?!
She's not a child. She can handle herself.
[in English] Let's go!
You go ahead. I'll look for Karla.
Gavin, I'm your girlfriend!
Karla is my friend!
She's my responsibility too!
[heavy music playing]
Gavin!
[in English] Cath, you better watch out.
Maybe Gavin likes Karla now.
[in English] Shut up.
[music fades]
Put that there.
- Yes. [indistinct]
- [indistinct]
- Be, one juice.
- Yes, I'll handle it.
Here's the payment.
[sighs] What's happening in our barangay?
Earlier, there was a shootout.
And now, Ibyang almost had an accident!
- [Siony sighs]
- Cita, how's Ibyang?
[sighs] Atoy and I went to the hospital.
We're home now.
Ibyang is resting.
I just went out again
because Karla hasn't come home.
- [suspicious music playing]
- You know, I didn't see her all day.
[in English] Oh? What are you guys
doing outside?!
[in English] This is not
the time for gossip.
- [in English] It's dangerous right now.
- Uh…
[Nestor, in English] Yes, we know.
[in English] But I was there
when they went, um, ah--
[imitates a gun firing sound]
[in English] The house of Paldo!
They shot up Paldo's house.
There, right there.
Brother Kurt, have you seen Karla?
[in English] Ah, yes.
[in English] She, uh,
was with Denden and her friends.
[in English] I think they went
to some, uh, disco bar.
So don't worry, miss,
Karla is safe with Denden.
[rousing music playing]
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunfire]
[gunfire]
[clacking]
[snipping]
[music swells]
[electronic blipping]
- [music fades]
- [indistinct]
[Karla] It looks fun inside.
No, it's more fun there.
- We're going to a more fun club.
- [sinister music playing]
We're going there.
We have more friends there.
- Okay. I'll just tell my friends first.
- No, don't bother.
- No, let's go.
- Let's go, come with us.
No, so they'll know where I am.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- [boy 1] Get in.
Where are you taking her?
- Don't meddle here.
- Gavin.
[boy 2] Just leave.
Karla is my friend. I'll take her home.
Karla, let's go.
Don't meddle, bro. Don't meddle.
- Just leave.
- [Gavin] Karla, come on.
- [boy 2] You're annoying.
- [boy 2] Karla is coming with us.
- [Gavin] What?
- Don't meddle.
[Karla] Gavin!
- [boy 1] Karla is coming with us.
- Bro, bro, relax.
[ominous music playing]
- [grunting and groaning]
- [Karla shrieks]
Come here! [grunts]
[boy 1] Ouch.
- [boy 1 grunts]
- What?! You want to fight?!
- No. Sorry.
- No. Bro, let's go.
- [boy 1] Sorry.
- Oh?
[boy 1 gunts]
Let's go, Karla.
[music concludes]
Gavin, thank you.
Why did you go with them?
You don't even know them.
They were nice to me.
But when I saw them ganging up on you,
they weren't nice anymore.
- They became enemies.
- [gentle music playing]
They're nice to you
because they have other motives.
Can you imagine? What if you were drunk?
Then you'd have no defense against them.
I'm sorry!
I didn't know.
It's my first time doing things like this.
At least, I could tell my problems
to them without judgment.
Why tell them?
I'm here.
[melancholic music playing]
Cathy doesn't want me near you, so…
Don't worry about Cathy.
Before I met her, we were already friends.
And no matter what you're going through,
I won't judge you.
Anything?
[in English] Promise?
[in English] Promise.
Even if we're deceiving people?
Even if I'm the child of a mistress?
[music swells]
Your own man eluded you?
[in English] He knows how you operate.
What if he reports to the police?
I'm not worried about the police.
[mysterious music playing]
I'm worried he might tell Atoy.
[sighs] What about him again?
Look. The vehicle Paldo used was Atoy's.
I don't know
how deep their connection is.
But if he doesn't go to the police,
he might talk to Atoy.
[scoffs, in English] What can Atoy do?
[in English] Hon, he's just one man!
[in English] Yes.
He's already ruined
many of our operations.
Remember our ivory smuggling
business before?
[gunfire blasting]
He's the reason that was exposed.
[in English] Okay. Well, then… [sighs]
[in English] Do something about this Atoy
before anything happens.
[Martina sighs]
- [Martina] Mmm…
- [music fades]
[Audrey] What will you do to Atoy?
[tense music playing]
Are you planning
something bad against Atoy?
We were just talking about him.
[mysterious music playing]
Someone shot people at Mongki's place.
And the vehicle used was Atoy's.
[suspicious music playing]
Why would he shoot Mongki?
Not unless Mongki struck first,
and he was just acting in self-defense.
Since you and Atoy separated
eight years ago,
you only had a few days with him.
[in English] So… [scoffs] you don't
really know him that well.
[in English] For all you know,
he's a criminal.
[in English] I don't think so.
[sighs] You're just too in love!
[in English] That's why everything
seems so right with this man.
Think carefully about who
you let into your life
and into Janine's life.
[in English] I may not
know him that well right now.
[in English] But what I do know…
[pensive music playing]
…is that he's nothing like you.
Okay. Then I'm a bad person.
But what if he is too?
You still don't know him that well.
- [clicks tongue]
- [tense music playing]
[in English] Let's go.
[music fades]
So, your real father
is Brother Atoy's father?
- [sniffs]
- [in English] That makes him
your half-brother.
Don't you want that?
[in English] Haven't you always looked up
to Brother Atoy as an older brother?
I do want Brother Atoy
to be my real brother.
Just not having different moms,
and he doesn't even know.
[pensive music playing]
Mom asked me not to tell him.
That made it harder for me.
[mellow music playing]
I get you.
That's hard because
the fact that you know the truth
and you have to act normal.
[in English] That's lying itself.
I wish I had known earlier,
so I could have known him better,
my real father.
That's what I regret.
The time we lost.
You can still do that.
Not with Sir Delfin,
but with Brother Atoy.
[in English] You know what?
[in English] Why not
get to know him better?
[in English] Spend time with him.
He's still your brother,
even if you're the only one who knows.
And don't think your friends
will judge you just because of that.
I'm pretty sure they'll accept you,
no matter what.
[gentle music playing]
Gavin, thank you.
I didn't really need alcohol
or to dress like this.
It suits you, though.
You could use that for basketball.
[chuckles]
There!
You're finally smiling.
I missed that too.
You're beautiful when you smile.
- Be quiet now.
- [chuckles]
You're annoying.
[music fades]
- Godmother.
- Hmm?
Is Ibyang asleep?
What are you waiting for?
Karla's still not here?
Uh, she went out with Denden,
Kurt's godchild.
I tried calling, but I couldn't reach her.
Even Karla's phone is off.
Where did she go?
And I haven't seen Karla for a long time.
What's happening to her?
[pensive music playing]
[music fades]
Psst, hey.
[clicks tongue] Where did you come from?
[pensive music playing]
I thought you were with Denden?
Uh, Brother Atoy, Denden left,
so I just accompanied Karla.
Where did you go? And why…
Why are you dressed like that?
It looks like you ran out of fabric.
We have plenty of fabric here.
Sister Denden just lent it to me,
and it was a bar.
[Atoy, in English] Bar?
[suspicious music playing]
[Cita] Uh…
Come on. Let's go home.
Come on. You should've at least texted.
There was a shootout.
I didn't know who to call to find you.
Come on. Let's go home.
Gavin, thank you.
[Cita] Let's go.
What was the shootout about?
- Who caused trouble?
- You don't need to know.
Gavin, you have other friends, right?
I want you to stay away from Karla.
Brother Atoy, I don't have
bad intentions toward Karla.
I know.
I don't need to explain myself to you.
Believe me.
This is better for her.
And also, do you know
where your father will be tomorrow?
I just need to ask him something.
[suave theme music playing]
[music intensifies]
[music fades]
Buddy, you can take a break.
Perfect. I'm hungry.
- Wait. Sir, hold on.
- Sir, sir, sir, sir, just a moment.
Sir.
Sir, wait!
Sir, who are you looking for, sir?
[tense music playing]
[grunting and groaning]
[grunts]
[music fades]
[Mongki] We searched all possible
hiding places of Paldo last night, boss.
Nothing.
He has no relatives here in Manila.
- [ominous music playing]
- [Mongki sighs]
Follow him to the province.
[sniffs]
Is that the gun?
[in English] Yes, boss.
[anxious music playing]
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
[car revving and tires screeching]
[crashes]
[car revving]
[music swells]
[phone ringing]
[music concludes]
Gavin? How are you?
Ah, your jacket.
Just get it at the house, okay.
Um, Karla, just keep it for now.
Last night Brother Atoy told me
not to go near you.
I'm scared of him. [sighs]
- [gentle music playing]
- Huh? Why?
[Gavin] He said it's for your own good.
Did I do something wrong?
I didn't abandon you last night.
[in English] Weird.
Brother Atoy isn't usually like that.
What else did he say to you?
He's looking for my father.
Do they have an issue?
I don't know.
You know, just let Brother Atoy be.
He's just intimidating us
because I stayed out late.
Gavin, thank you again last night.
- [pleasant music playing]
- I miss bonding with you.
[in English] I missed you too.
Next time again, okay.
[music fades]
[suspicious music playing]
[soft grunt]
Hey!
What are you doing here?
Audrey isn't here--
Don't meddle here.
Move aside!
[tense music playing]
Come here.
Call the guard. Make Atoy leave.
[in English] Yes, ma'am.
[music fades]
- [horn honks]
- Oh, needle!
What-- What is that?!
[pensive music playing]
Karla, let's talk.
No "good morning" at all?
There's nothing good about the morning,
except for those who steal.
[in English] So, what?
[in English] Are you trying
to steal my boyfriend?
Cathy, Gavin and I are just friends.
I won't steal him from you.
[in English] Oh, please, Karla!
You really think I don't notice
the way you look at him?
That you're not really happy
that we became a couple.
I don't know what you're saying.
[in English] Of course,
you're going to deny it.
[in English] But actions
speak louder than words, Karla.
That's why you acted
like a damsel in distress last night,
so Gavin would be forced
to choose you over me.
I didn't force him
to be with me last night.
You stay there!
[in English] I'm not finished yet!
Let me go!
Wow, an early confrontation.
- Yes.
- Hey, let's take a video.
- Hurry, hurry, girl.
- [indistinct]
[phone blips]
[suspicious music playing]
Didn't you talk to Atoy?
He left. I thought he was going to you.
Ah, he texted me last night.
He told us to come here.
So why did he leave?
Um, maybe he just bought something.
Sit down first while waiting.
- [sighs]
- Ah, Mommy, I'll just go to the CR.
- I need to pee.
- Okay.
I'll go with you.
Ah, no. It's fine. I know where it is.
All right.
Audrey, sit down.
- Okay, thank you.
- [Emerson] Miss.
- Oh?
- Where's Atoy?
He left. Didn't say where he was going.
Oh, no. [clicks tongue]
I didn't catch him.
Who knows what he'll do.
- What?
- What do you mean?
Is he okay?
Audrey, uh, what are you doing here?
He told me and Janine to come here.
He said we'd have lunch out,
but he's not here.
Ah, what's happening, Emerson?
[tense music playing]
Ah, ah-- Audrey…
[inhales]
Didn't Atoy tell you? [inhales]
He knows who killed his father.
- [gasps]
- [music fades]
- Your brother, Red.
- [Cita gasps]
[intense music playing]
[Emerson] Yes.
He wanted to go after Red last night, but…
we stopped him.
But now it looks like we can't anymore.
[music fades]
This is great.
[chuckles] Of course, boss.
I have good news, boss.
Hmm?
Remember Sister Norma,
who suddenly disappeared?
My guy found out she moved to the province
and came to Manila a week ago!
She stayed with relatives.
[mysterious music playing]
You found her?
Roger is looking for her.
He'll update me later.
[energetic rock music playing]
- [Red sighs]
- [music fades]
[henchman] Hey!
What are you doing here?!
[groaning]
[Mongki] Boss, boss, let's go!
[grunting and groaning]
[in English] Martina, what's happening?
- [in English] Dad--
- Is there a shootout?
[in English] We have a problem.
[in English] Atoy is here.
And I think he's after Red!
- [line ringing]
- [sighs]
[softly, in English]
Pick up, pick up, pick up.
- [line rings]
- [phone ringing]
[in English] Hello, Audrey.
Atoy is here at the trucking compound.
Do you know why he's here?
[in English] What?
Ah, Dad, is Red there?
[sighs] They can't meet.
He's the one Atoy is looking for here.
Dad, Red killed Atoy's father.
That's why he's there,
to go after Red.
[in English] Sir.
Sir Red is fighting with someone.
[employee] They're shooting
at each other at the firing range.
Dad, stop Atoy! [gasps]
[employee] Some of our guards
are already dead.
What the-- Dad.
- [in English] Come on, let's go. Let's go.
- [in English] Let's go.
[gasps] Um, Miss Cita,
can I leave Janine with you for now?
I'll just go to Atoy, okay?
- Audrey…
- You can--
Atoy has no allies at your place.
Don't abandon him, okay?
[tense music playing]
- [Emerson mutters]
- [Audrey gasps]
[sighs] My God.
Miss…
to be honest, I don't think that…
Eh, I'm not worried
that Atoy has no allies there.
With how furious Atoy is,
some innocent lives
might get entangled in it too.
My God. [gasps]
[gasping]
My God.
- [growls]
- [gunshots]
[growls]
[grunts]
[grunting and groaning]
[growls]
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
[grunting and groaning]
You animal.
I know the truth now.
You killed my father!
[rousing music playing]
You know, this is what
should be done to women
- who are sluts like you!
- [shrieks, grunting]
[Karla] What is this?!
[clamoring]
[Karla] Stop it, Cathy!
- [grunts]
- [Karla] What?!
[soft rock music playing]
[Cathy grunts]
[grunting]
That's Karla! Oh!
- Oh, no, there she is.
- [shrieks]
- Hurry, let's go to her!
- [gasping]
[clamoring]
[Karla] Let me go!
[Jona] Stop it, stop it!
[grunts]
[grunting and groaning]
My father did nothing wrong to you.
I will kill you!
[growls and grunts]
[tense music playing]
- You're really an animal!
- [Dmitri] Red!
- [growls]
- [Martina, in English] Stop him!
[Martina, in English] Stop it, Dad! Dad!
- [groaning]
- [Martina, in English] Oh my God, Red!
- [growling]
- [Martina gasps]
- [groans]
- [shrieks]
[growls]
Stop hurting my child!
[in English] Stay away
from my husband! [gasps]
[in English] Hon, get up.
[in English] Get up, hon! Please, please!
- [in English] Get up.
- [Red grunts]
[pensive music playing]
Your son killed my father.
[music swells]
My father had cancer then.
But I wish he had just let my father live,
so I could have spent more time with him.
[in English] I'm sorry,
but you have to stop this.
You can't get your father back
if you kill Red.
That's not what I want. [inhales]
What I want…
[gasps]
What I want is revenge.
He didn't just take a life, he took time.
Time I could have spent with my father.
So, I will kill your son.
[scoffs, gasps]
If you were in my position, huh?
[scoffs]
What would you do?
What?
I would kill too.
[in English] But he's still my son.
[in English] It's my duty to protect him.
[in English] We do
what we have to do for family.
[scoffs]
[in English] Family?
Don't worry.
‪[gasps]
I won't involve you.
[music swells]
[sharp exhale]
But your son, I will kill him.
[music fades]
[screams]
[tense music playing]
[gasps]
[electronic blipping]
[tense music playing]
- [Ibyang] Tatoy.
- [Janine] Daddy?
[Cita] What happened?
What happened to your hand?
- Is that blood?
- It's nothing.
[Gavin] He shot my grandfather.
He beat up my father!
Your father deserved it!
He killed Sir Delfin,
Brother Atoy's and my dad!
What evidence does your brother
have to accuse him, huh?
He's just like your father.
They're both pretenders!
What you're saying is foul!
I pity you.
I know you're a good kid.
You're just surrounded by liars.
You're the ones who are pitiful!
There are more liars around you!
Why don't you ask Karla?!
What? What about Karla?
[Atoy] What is that?
Are you having something sewn?
‪UP NEXT
[woman shrieks] Hey!
[shrieking]
Did Red send you, huh?
- Who sent you?
- Help, help!
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias